http://www.womeninprogress.org/Info/privacynotice

My Account
Face MasksSALEWomenFall 2020DressesSkirtsTopsRobesFashion Accessories View AllMenShirtsBoxers View AllKidsBaby CollectionBabiesGirlsBoysKids' Accessories View AllJewelryNecklacesBraceletsEarringsBeads View AllAccessoriesBags + PursesClutches + WalletsTravel CasesSarongsFashion Accessories View AllHome2020 Home CollectionAprons + PotholdersEco Flour Sack CollectionKitchen + DiningStorageDécor + AccentsGift BagsWater HyacinthBooks + Stationary View AllOrnamentsBath + BodySlippery Slope Shea ButterTrunk Scrub Shea SoapDandy Lion African Black SoapBulk Shea Butter View AllPets
New Customer
My Account
Shop
Face MasksSALEWomenFall 2020DressesSkirtsTopsRobesFashion Accessories View AllMenShirtsBoxers View AllKidsBaby CollectionBabiesGirlsBoysKids' Accessories View AllJewelryNecklacesBraceletsEarringsBeads View AllAccessoriesBags + PursesClutches + WalletsTravel CasesSarongsFashion Accessories View AllHome2020 Home CollectionAprons + PotholdersEco Flour Sack CollectionKitchen + DiningStorageDécor + AccentsGift BagsWater HyacinthBooks + Stationary View AllOrnamentsBath + BodySlippery Slope Shea ButterTrunk Scrub Shea SoapDandy Lion African Black SoapBulk Shea Butter View AllPets
Privacy Policy
PRIVACY POLICY
Global Mamas is committed to your privacy. We do not collect personally identifying information about you when you visit our site, unless you choose to provide such information to us through a online form or through making an online purchase. Providing such information is strictly voluntary.
INFORMATION COLLECTING, USE & SHARING
We collect and store only the following information about you: the name of the domain from which you access the Internet; the date and time you access our site; and the Internet address of the web site from which you linked to our site. We use the information to measure the number of visitors to the different sections of our site, and to help us make our site more useful to visitors. Our site uses cookies to keep track of your shopping cart. We use cookies to identify you so we can retrieve your information so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site.
In order to provide feedback to or request information from Global Mamas, you may fill out an online form or send us an email that shares your personal information. This information will be used to process the related request. Your contact information will only be used to send non-order related e-mails if you have subscribed to the e-mail list. You may opt-out of receiving future mailings by sending us an email that you would like to un-subscribe.
YOUR ACCESS TO & CONTROL OVER INFORMATION
We will not share your name or email address with any outside parties (except as might be required by law). You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:
•    See what data we have about you, if any.
•    Change/correct any data we have about you.
•    Have us delete any data we have about you.
•    Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
SECURITY ON OUR SITE
The Global Mamas site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. All data is protected using the most advanced methods available. Ordering online with us is safe and secure. Credit card orders are processed through our secure online Internet gateway, Authorize.net. We do not store financial information like credit card numbers or personal information like social security numbers on this site.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 612-781-0455 or via email at wholesale@globalmamas.org
CC
Wholesale
Wholesale-Europe
Wholesale-Australia
Fair Trade
Meet the Mamas
Volunteer
Shop Online
